sosodesktop.com 2017-05-23

# Privacy

### PRIVACY POLICY

This Privacy Policy explains how SoSoDesk.com (the “Site”, “us” or “we”), a website developed & owned by Bysenda Technology Limited, uses and protects information that you (“you” or “user”) provide us when you use web pages on our Site. If you have questions or comments regarding this Campaign Privacy Policy, please contact us at contact@bysenda.com.

## How We Obtain Your Information:

We get information about you in a range of ways. Information You Give Us. We collect information you directly give us on the web pages designated, which may include information such as your first and last name, company, company mailing address, telephone number and email address etc.

## Information We Get from Others

We may get information about you from other sources, such as social media like Twitter, LinkedIn, etc. When you click on our ads placed with them, they will provide us with information from your accounts there (including your first and last name, social media handle and email address) to enhance and personalize your use of this Site.

## Information Automatically Collected

We may automatically log information about you and your computer. For example, when you visit our Site, we may log your device operating system type, browser type, browser language, pages you viewed, how long you spent on a page, access times, and information about your use of and actions on our Site. 

## Cookies

We may log information using “cookies.” Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive by a website. Cookies help us make your visit better. We use cookies to see which parts of our Site people use and like and to count visits to our Site.  A cookie cannot give access to your computer or any information stored on your computer. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

## How We Use Your Information

The information we collect on the web pages may be used for any of the following purposes: To verify your identity. To correspond with you in the future (such as through emails, mail or other correspondence, including to market our products and services and products and services of our partners, customers and clients, and to promote upcoming events or news).  To operate, maintain, and improve our Site, products, and services of our partners, customers and clients. 

We will not sell your personal information to any persons or organizations except in the event we negotiate a transaction involving the sale or transfer of all or other corporate change in control.  We will not share your personal information with anyone other than our authorized third-party vendors who need it to provide services for us, or when required by law or legal process, or for the investigation of illegal or criminal activities, or the exercise of our legal rights in defense against any legal claims, or otherwise.

## Controlling Your Personal Information

Upon written request, we will give you access to review any of your personal information that we have and to allow you to correct any inaccuracies or to remove your personal information, provided it is not required to be retained for our valid business purposes. We will require you to identify yourself and the information you request to access, remove, modify or correct before commencing such requests.  
To request access, correction or removal of your personal information, please contact contact@bysenda.com. We will verify by email to you that we have corrected or removed your requested information.

## Updates and Changes to this Campaign Privacy Policy

Occasionally, we may change this Campaign Privacy Policy. We will post a notification on the Site and will also revise the ‘last updated date’ within this Privacy Policy. Changes will take effect from the date they are posted.   Your continued use of the Site constitutes your ongoing agreement to this Campaign Privacy Policy and any updates.

## For any questions or concerns you may have regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us

_Adress:_ ROOM 1103, HANG SENG MONGKOK BUILDING 677 NATHAN ROAD MONGKOK, KLN，HONG KONG

_Email:_[Contact@bysenda.com](mailto:Contact@bysenda.com)
